In celestial majesty mountains stand tall
their peaks pierce the heavens beyond earthly
thrall like ancient sentinels they
reach for the sky their summits ablaze with a glorious
hue forever high through mist and cloud
their rugged forms emerge a symphony of
stone nature's grandest surge. In silent awe
we gaze upon their might a testament to times relentless
flight beneath their gaze, valleys unfurl
like verdant scrolls where life unfolds
its tapestry a symphony of souls
rivers weave through emerald landscapes a silver
thread connecting the heavens to the earth a mystical
thread. As the sun sinks low, casting golden
rays mountains become beacons ablaze
with celestial praise their summits glow with ethereal
fire a testament to nature's boundless desire
in the face of adversity they stand unyielding
their strength a reminder forever wielding they
symbolize aspiration reaching for the unknown inspiring
hearts to soar where dreams are sown. So let us marvel
at these celestial wonders grand mountains
touching the sky a sight that fills the land.
In their presence, awe and wonder ignite
a reminder that even in the darkest of nights the spirit
of the mountains will always burn brighten.