Mountains reaching towards the heavens a symbol of
strength and eternal presence. They stand tall,
defying times, erosion a testament to natures
unwavering devotion. Majestic peaks enveloped
in clouds. Their rocky summits pierce the celestial shrouds.
Each crag and crevice a story untold of
ancient battles and mysteries yet to unfold.
Their slopes adorned with vibrant hues from
verdant meadows to skies of endless blues.
Waterfalls cascade with thunderous might carving
canyons deep a breathtaking sight.
In winters embrace they don a pristine white a
canvas painted with snowflakes pure and bright.
Yet when spring awakens life bursts forth
anew transforming slopes into a vibrant,
verdant hui. Hikers and climbers ascend their rugged
frame seeking solace and adventure in nature's game.
Each step they take a pilgrimage to the sky
where earth meets heaven and dreams soar high.
Oh mountain range, your glory knows no
bounds. Your peaks forever reaching towards celestial
grounds a beacon of hope, a reminder
to aspire, to touch the heavens with passion and
desiree.